<?xml version = '1.0'?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="xmp.xsl"?>
<TAGLIST>
<HEADER>
<title>XMP tags defined in Exiv2</title>
<text>
<p>Some description</p>
<p>Click on a column header to sort the table.</p>
</text>
</HEADER>
<ROWSET>
   <ROW num="1">
      <tagname>DerivedFrom</tagname>
      <title>Derived From</title>
      <xmpvaltype>ResourceRef</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>A reference to the original document from which this one is derived. It is a minimal reference; missing components can be assumed to be unchanged. For example, a new version might only need to specify the instance ID and version number of the previous version, or a rendition might only need to specify the instance ID and rendition class of the original.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="2">
      <tagname>DocumentID</tagname>
      <title>Document ID</title>
      <xmpvaltype>URI</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>The common identifier for all versions and renditions of a document. It should be based on a UUID; see Document and Instance IDs below.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="3">
      <tagname>History</tagname>
      <title>History</title>
      <xmpvaltype>seq ResourceEvent</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpSeq</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>An ordered array of high-level user actions that resulted in this resource. It is intended to give human readers a general indication of the steps taken to make the changes from the previous version to this one. The list should be at an abstract level; it is not intended to be an exhaustive keystroke or other detailed history.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="4">
      <tagname>Ingredients</tagname>
      <title>Ingredients</title>
      <xmpvaltype>bag ResourceRef</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpBag</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>References to resources that were incorporated, byinclusion or reference, into this resource.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="5">
      <tagname>InstanceID</tagname>
      <title>Instance ID</title>
      <xmpvaltype>URI</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>An identifier for a specific incarnation of a document, updated each time a file is saved. It should be based on a UUID; see Document and Instance IDs below.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="6">
      <tagname>ManagedFrom</tagname>
      <title>Managed From</title>
      <xmpvaltype>ResourceRef</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>A reference to the document as it was prior to becoming managed. It is set when a managed document is introduced to an asset management system that does not currently own it. It may or may not include references to different management systems.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="7">
      <tagname>Manager</tagname>
      <title>Manager</title>
      <xmpvaltype>AgentName</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>The name of the asset management system that manages this resource. Along with xmpMM: ManagerVariant, it tells applications which asset management system to contact concerning this document.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="8">
      <tagname>ManageTo</tagname>
      <title>Manage To</title>
      <xmpvaltype>URI</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>A URI identifying the managed resource to the asset management system; the presence of this property is the formal indication that this resource is managed. The form and content of this URI is private to the asset management system.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="9">
      <tagname>ManageUI</tagname>
      <title>Manage UI</title>
      <xmpvaltype>URI</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>A URI that can be used to access information about the managed resource through a web browser. It might require a custom browser plug-in.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="10">
      <tagname>ManagerVariant</tagname>
      <title>Manager Variant</title>
      <xmpvaltype>Text</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>Specifies a particular variant of the asset management system. The format of this property is private to the specific asset management system.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="11">
      <tagname>OriginalDocumentID</tagname>
      <title>Original Document ID</title>
      <xmpvaltype>URI</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>Refer to Part 1, Data Model, Serialization, and Core Properties, for definition.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="12">
      <tagname>Pantry</tagname>
      <title>Pantry</title>
      <xmpvaltype>bag struct</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>Each array item has a structure value with a potentially unique set of fields, containing extracted XMP from a component. Each field is a property from the XMP of a contained resource component, with all substructure preserved. Each pantry entry shall contain an xmpMM:InstanceID. Only one copy of the pantry entry for any given xmpMM:InstanceID shall be retained in the pantry. Nested pantry items shall be removed from the individual pantry item and promoted to the top level of the pantry.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="13">
      <tagname>RenditionClass</tagname>
      <title>Rendition Class</title>
      <xmpvaltype>RenditionClass</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>The rendition class name for this resource. This property should be absent or set to default for a document version that is not a derived rendition.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="14">
      <tagname>RenditionParams</tagname>
      <title>Rendition Params</title>
      <xmpvaltype>Text</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>Can be used to provide additional rendition parameters that are too complex or verbose to encode in xmpMM: RenditionClass.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="15">
      <tagname>VersionID</tagname>
      <title>Version ID</title>
      <xmpvaltype>Text</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>The document version identifier for this resource. Each version of a document gets a new identifier, usually simply by incrementing integers 1, 2, 3 . . . and so on. Media management systems can have other conventions or support branching which requires a more complex scheme.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="16">
      <tagname>Versions</tagname>
      <title>Versions</title>
      <xmpvaltype>seq Version</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>The version history associated with this resource. Entry [1] is the oldest known version for this document, entry [last()] is the most recent version. Typically, a media management system would fill in the version information in the metadata on check-in. It is not guaranteed that a complete history  versions from the first to this one will be present in the xmpMM:Versions property. Interior version information can be compressed or eliminated and the version history can be truncated at some point.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="17">
      <tagname>LastURL</tagname>
      <title>Last URL</title>
      <xmpvaltype>URL</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>Deprecated for privacy protection.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="18">
      <tagname>RenditionOf</tagname>
      <title>Rendition Of</title>
      <xmpvaltype>ResourceRef</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>Deprecated in favor of xmpMM:DerivedFrom. A reference to the document of which this is a rendition.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
   <ROW num="19">
      <tagname>SaveID</tagname>
      <title>Save ID</title>
      <xmpvaltype>Integer</xmpvaltype>
      <type>XmpText</type>
      <category>Internal</category>
      <tagdesc>Deprecated. Previously used only to support the xmpMM:LastURL property.</tagdesc>
   </ROW>
</ROWSET>
</TAGLIST>
